<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content"><channel><title>Sergei Nazarenko</title><description>Блог о программировании и не только</description><link>https://nazares.github.io</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 16:36:16 +0300</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 16:36:16 +0300</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="https://nazares.github.io/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://nazares.github.io/articles/introduction-en</guid><title>New Blog</title><description>Hello! Now I have a Blog and this is  my first note. I will write here different articles about computer programming languages and tech.</description><link>https://nazares.github.io/articles/introduction-en</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 03:02:00 +0300</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>My New Blog</h1><p>Hello, Now I have a new blog, and this is my first post. I've never done it before but I'm going to write different articles about computer programming languages ​​and tech. So, Why do I need it? First of all it can help me to improve my communication skills and and let me not to forget about work I've already done. In third it may help some others to expand their knowledge and to find out something new. Sometimes I'll write in different languages, sometimes I'll use <span class="highlight red">Russian</span>, sometimes <span class="highlight blue">English</span>, so it will also help me to improve my English, because English is the second main language for programmers and as I've seen at the Internet a someone said "<span class="quote">A programmer wihout understanding English like a Surgeon Doctor without a scalpel - He can still do the surgery but not so perfect</span>". And I totally agree with that saying. There's no limit to perfection! PS: So wish me luck with that hard but very interesting way of writing, but I wish you Good Reading! Thanks for your attention.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://nazares.github.io/articles/introduction-ru</guid><title>Новый Блог</title><description>Привет! Теперь у меня есть Блог! И  это мой первый пост. Здесь я буду писать разные статьи о языках программирования и технологиях.</description><link>https://nazares.github.io/articles/introduction-ru</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 03:02:00 +0300</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Мой новый блог</h1><p>Привет! Теперь у меня есть свой блог! И это мой первый пост, я собираюсь здесь писать разные статьи о языках программирования и технологиях. Зачем мне это нужно?, Ну во-первых, это поможет мне развить и улучшить комуникативные (повествовательные) навыки, не забыть то, что уже наработано и в третих это возможно кому-то может быть полезным, поможет найти ответы или будет интересно узнать что-то новое. Иногда я буду писать как на <span class="highlight red">русском</span> так и на <span class="highlight blue">английском</span> языках - это так же является очень хорошей практикой в развитии навыков, ведь для разработчика (программиста), английский - это второй родной язык. Улышал как-то в интернете фразу <span class="quote">"Программист без английского - это все равно, что хирург без скальпеля, операцию конечно провести сможет, но крайне не качественно!"</span>. В целом я ее целиком и полностью поддерживаю! Совершенству предела нет! Так что, давайте развиваться и стремиться постичь <strong>禅, дзен</strong>. Как говорят <strong>французы</strong> : "- Just do it!" (шутка). Не французы... <span class="wp-font-emots-emo-happy"></span></p><p>PS: В общем пожелайте мне удачи в этом не легком но увлекательном деле, а вам желаю приятного чтения!</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>